If you go from end to end, if a patient
calls in, they book an appointment, then
what happens from there is they have to
get the insurance verified. And then
they book time with a doctor, they have
to come and see [music] the doctor for
the insurance companies. That's a whole
another whole another game there. Um and
then they submit the claims. They'll
probably get rejected because insurance
companies in America are not very good.
Um they go back and forth, they try to
get paid, it's 3 months later they get
their money, and it's a huge lag time.
And then from there they start to buy
all the drugs ahead of time so they have
to front [music] a lot of the money.
This is a huge problem in the in the
practice space. Um so just dealing with
all those things like end to end. Like
Nitro over all we're dealing with the
the financial aspect of it. And then we
also have the AI software that handles
the scheduling of the patients, the the
claims management um for the the
doctors, and also the insurance um
eligibility checks. So it's like we're
trying to do all these things end to end
so that for them it's just very easy.
They just see this whole thing happen um
handled by Nitro's AI. As we're going
this fast like what not to do is to hire
[music] fast. I think there's a saying,
right? Like hire fast, fire fast in
startups. And then I think it was
readjusted later because a lot of
startups made made that mistake. Um but
the real saying is hire slowly, fire
fast. And then when you hire folks,
[music]
always hire for uh the people, not for
the role. Always hire for like
intelligence and um people who can have
a wider range of doing things. Look, I
wouldn't say like a generalist but like
they just have more agency. They see a
problem, even if it's not, they'll just
fix it.
>> By themselves.
>> yeah. But then I think these kind of
people are
quite hard to find
to hire. Yeah.
>> That's why it's hire slowly cuz it takes
time.
>> [music]
>> Uh what should I say Fox?
Nit- Nitro
Johnson, say hi to everyone.
>> Hi guys, how are you doing? It's good
It's good to be on here.
>> Okay. Oh, okay. Johnson, can you tell us
our listeners what kind of company is
Nitra? Who do you help and what problem
do you solve?
>> Yeah,
well again, thanks for having me on
here.
It's really great
to be speaking here. So,
again, my name is Jonathan. Uh
I am the one of the co-founders of Nitra
and essentially Nitra is building an
all-in-one fintech and AI platform for
the healthcare space in the US market.
>> Mhm.
>> Um so, we primarily sell to doctors
um and practices in the US.
>> Okay. So, Nitra's story started in 2021
when you and the team were taking a walk
in Washington, D.C. What did you talk
about on the walk that made you think
this is a necessary thing we should
build?
>> Yeah, you know,
um
I think, you know, as we are getting
older,
in our 30s, right? I think in your 20s
you don't think about health as much.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> And as our parents are getting older,
we're starting to experience more of the
healthcare system in the US, which is a
lot worse than
Taiwan, for sure.
And
we just felt like there was just so
many, at least like
barriers and like technology like
issues, especially in the
in the back office of the practices.
>> Yes.
>> Um
and
for me personally, I was like dealing
with uh and and this was like 2021. I
was actually dealing with uh really bad
eczema. Um and even though, you know, I
I've been through
uh the healthcare system throughout my
entire life, it wasn't as
frequent as uh in in 2021.
Um
where I had to go try to figure out how
to go to the uh the dermatologist like
almost on a like a bi-weekly basis. Um
and it was just very difficult to book
time with them.
>> Mhm.
>> Um and it was very difficult to like
handle the insurance process.
>> Mhm.
>> Um and then uh outside that, um my mom
was actually getting worse as well in
terms of her health and I was frequently
trying to deal with all the aspects of
getting her treatment and like for her
it was even worse because it would
actually take 6 months, like months just
to book appointments and then you know,
the whole process was a pain in the
butt. So, it was like my own personal
experience with
dealing with my own um
skin issues
>> Mhm.
>> and it was already very painful.
>> Yeah.
>> Um and then also as my mom was getting
older, a lot of different hospital
visits um and figuring that stuff out.
So, we start I started to think more
because like as as you get older, you
start to be exposed to this a lot more.
Um these are sort of really big issues.
If we're dealing this dealing with this
and these are like small problems, I
can't imagine like
you know, the rest of the world or rest
of um the folks dealing with these
issues, but for larger
um issues and problems.
>> Above 25% of the FiscalNote customers
come from healthcare.
Uh
what problems did you see in those
customers that other software still was
not fixing because I I think there are a
lot of the software are trying to fix
similar problem, but the
what's the difference?
>> Yeah, no, that's a that's a good
question. Um
I guess like with FiscalNote, we were a
just to give context to the audience, uh
FiscalNote was my first company. Um
we basically at FiscalNote we were
government tech and AI. We were actually
doing LLMs before it was a thing, but we
it was on a smaller scale. So, I guess
you'd call it uh small language models.
>> [laughter]
>> Um cuz we only dealt with like
government data um in that space. So, we
were doing a lot of prediction and and
machine learning back then. Um and you
know, we sold to a lot of healthcare
systems who are dealing with high
regulation. So, what our thing for
FiscalNote was dealing with regulations
and helping businesses and organizations
deal with regulations.
Um so,
I guess like during those relationships,
we noticed that the healthcare industry
just spends a lot of money
but very very inefficiently. Um
which sort of got us thinking more about
like, "Okay, well,
uh we know the healthcare system is
really screwed for the patient side or
really not
uh the not ideal experience for the
patients. But part of that reason is
because on the back office or on the
practice sides practice side, it's
really inefficient. Right? They're
spending a lot of wasted money. They're
spending a lot of wasted time on dealing
with insurance companies and all these
supplies and drugs and the supply chain
um to get all these, you know, drugs in.
It's just very inefficient.
Right? So,
that kind of
caused the I guess like us to think
about, "Okay, well, what if we instead
of doing what everyone else does, which
is usually a lot of startups they go
after the patient side first.
>> Yeah.
>> So, they try to go after the patient
experience first. It's very very or
>> Naturally.
>> Yeah, naturally. It's very sat-
saturated.
>> Saturated. Okay.
>> Right, saturated. Um so, there's a lot
of players, but there're not a lot of
players who are dealing with, for
example, like the back office, the
expense side, the spending, the
procurement, the drug purchasing. So, we
felt like it was a very uh what do you
call a a blue ocean environment more so,
um meaning that there's not as much
competition, not as much people going
into this kind of, you know,
specific area in the practice. And we
decided, "Hey, why don't we
really dive in, dive into the this
portion first, and then kind of move
into the patient side?" Which is
actually what we're doing right now.
>> Mhm. Mhm. Mhm. So, Nitdoc itself, the
AI operation system for health care's
practice. Can you walk us through one
day of the doctor's work, and show us
where Nitdoc fits in?
>> Yeah.
Um
So, a few things.
Uh
I guess like there's sort of three main
workflows that we're focused on.
Um
to summarize like what a doctor deals
with, right? Um
So, uh and when I say doctor, I mean the
the whole practice um as a whole. The
doctor is actually mostly just seeing
the patients every single day. And they
actually let the office managers and the
office staff handle all the
administrative work. Right? Um so,
essentially there there's sort of three
areas. One is like, you know, handling
the patients,
um the scheduling, the insurance, all
these all these areas, and dealing with
claims, and getting paid, right? So,
that's sort of like one area that the
office managers have to deal with,
right? Cuz they have to get paid, they
deal with the patient side.
Um then they have to deal with, for
example, uh the purchasing lifestyle.
They have to Okay, well, you know, if
they book a patient, if it's a
specialist, they have to order certain
drugs, like in eye care, they have to
order a lot of eye care drugs
um for their patients.
Um so, they're dealing with all these
uh purchasing workflows and procurement,
um and inventory management, and
spending a lot of money on probably
dozens, if not hundreds, of vendors.
Um
So, these are kind of like uh if you go
from end to end, if a patient calls in,
they book an appointment
then what happens from there is they
have to get their insurance
verified
and that usually happens on the
uh
on the the admin side the
the office admin usually calls the
insurance companies verifies the
eligibility of
>> [snorts]
>> their insurance and then
they book time with the doctor then they
come and see the doctor you know there's
a lot of actually startups here where
they do like the describing of you know
what is being said in those
conversations so that you can do medical
coding for the insurance companies
that's a whole another whole another
game there
and then they submit the claims they'll
probably get rejected because the
insurance companies in America are not
very good uh
they go back and forth they try to get
paid it's 3 months later they get their
money and it's a huge lag time and then
from there they still have to buy all
the drugs ahead of time so they have to
front a lot of the money to buy the
materials and drugs ahead of time even
though they get paid a lot later through
insurance so this is a huge problem in
the in the practice space
so just dealing with all those things
like end to end like Nitra
overall we're dealing with the
the financial aspect of it so the
spending
the expense management
all the all the financial workflows
we're also dealing with and and handling
the the purchasing side so we deal with
the drugs we sell the drugs we sell the
medical supplies and then we also have
the ASR where they handle the scheduling
the patients the the claims management
for the the doctors and also the
insurance
eligibility checks so it's like we're
trying to do all these things end to end
so that
for them it's just very easy they just
see this whole thing happen
handled by Nitra's AI and they can just
kind of you know relax a little bit more
>> Okay
Um sounds like a great solution for for
the health chaos. So, you have said that
uh most health care software only
handles paperwork and the billing, but
that does not solve the real running
problems of the the
clinic. In your mind, what's the real
difference between AI native and the old
school software with AI add add on it?
>> Yeah.
Yeah, I think, you know,
I I guess I to rephrase, I think there's
a lot of startups doing very, very
specific things. Like there's probably a
lot of startups doing just patient
scheduling. There's a lot of startups
doing just like, for example, claims
management. And there's a lot of
startups doing like medical coding
for the the claims, right? And they
probably
And then the coding part is really
difficult because
you have so many different specialties
that have so many different nuances,
right? Like, you know, the best way is
actually just go at it one specialty at
a time and then still it would take
forever to just to code how much one
specialty.
So,
the way I think the future is like um,
and you're actually starting to see this
cuz a lot of the big VC firms, uh, like
the tier one VCs like A16Z and
everybody,
they think the I think they published
like a paper on this or like a post on
this, right?
>> did. Yeah.
>> It talked about how like it's services,
um, that are going to become more and
more prominent. So, what that means is,
um, instead of trying to sell the AI
software,
uh, you know, instead of me going to a
practice and saying, "Hey, let me sell
you this AI software that will do this,
I don't know, claims management for
you."
>> Mhm.
>> Right? It's kind of like, "Well, I don't
trust it 100% because there's all these
small little details that the humans
know." So, instead, the future is,
um,
"Hey, we're going to come and we're
going to take over this entire process
for you.
You don't have to worry. You pay us the
same as you would have Well, like we'll
staff the members to do this part for
you. Mhm. you pay us the same amount and
then we're to replace it with AI over
time, and then we share the the savings.
>> Oh.
>> Right? So, then you will ease into kind
of this new way of doing things, and
then the AI will improve over time. But
then in your mind, you know that there's
still somewhat a human involved um
who are going to really help, I guess,
uh or not help like cause them to worry
so much about like the inaccuracies of
the AI.
>> Mhm.
>> Um and we think that potentially, you
know, coming in with a services-based
approach could be the future of how we
ease more folks into, you know, the
world of AI.
>> Yeah. And then you still have people,
human, in the loop, right?
>> Yeah, I mean, we're we're thinking about
this right now. Um we're already talking
with a bunch of clients.
>> Mhm.
>> And we're saying like, "Hey, why don't
we just take over this entire process?
We'll just do it."
>> Mhm.
>> And whether we use AI or not is not your
concern.
>> Mhm.
>> Um the result will be the same, and we
have to deal with all the problems.
>> Okay. Um in 2025, uh Nitro grew more
than 700
>> 40%
>> 40% in revenue, and the now handles over
1 billion [snorts]
with a year. Um when the company is
growing so fast, is there anything you
choose not to do? And that choice
actually helps you grow in a health way.
>> I guess uh add more context. We in 2025
start 2025, we had about 4 million
revenue, and then at the end of 2025,
basically start 2026, we ended at like
33 million
>> Wow.
>> um in revenue. And then you're right,
like we processed about a billion
dollars uh in transactions.
>> Mhm.
>> Um
and
as we're going this fast, like
what not to do is to hire fast. I mean,
I think there's a saying, right? Like
hire fast, fire fast in startups. And
then I think it was readjusted later
because a lot of startups made made that
mistake. Um but the real saying is hire
slowly, fire fast.
Um and then when you hire people, folks,
always hire for
uh the people, not for the role. Um
I think uh there was a great VC, I
forgot his name, who who mentioned this
like [laughter]
uh
always hire for like
intelligence and um people who can have
a wider range of doing things instead of
a very specific role cuz then you just
If you do that, you start to fill
fill up the company with people who
will
if problems happen adjacently,
they'll just be like, "Oh, that's not my
job. You need to hire someone else."
Right? Versus um someone who's really
good um who's Look, I wouldn't say like
a generalist, but like they just have
more agency. They see a problem. Even if
it's not They will just fix it.
By themselves.
>> But then, I I think these kind of people
are quite hard to find.
They're hard
>> That's why it's hire slowly cuz it takes
time.
>> But the don't you think um
because of AI, so you don't need to hire
so many people? Uh uh compared to maybe
10 years ago.
>> I agree.
>> Agree. Okay.
>> Um but the the caveat there is also
you need to hire So, the AI landscape is
changing so fast. I think we all know
this.
Right? It's It's like even just a month
ago, it's like it's the problem right
now is not about like, "Okay, yes, we
know AI is here to do a lot of things."
The problem is it's so fragmented right
now and it's changing so fast. Like I
don't even like I'm trying to keep up
right now and I think everyone's trying
to keep up right now.
Uh the the younger people have an
advantage cuz they're not They don't
have to actually do work, so they can
just sit there and just play around with
it.
Fresh mind.
>> Right.
Everything. Yeah, yeah, [laughter] yeah.
And play around. They have more time to
play.
>> yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
>> But it's hard for us in the workforce
cuz we still have to get our job done,
but then is it Sometimes it takes more
time to figure out how to do it through
AI
than to just do it yourself. So, we're
in this loop
>> So, there is no best practice right now.
>> Yes.
>> You only can
You only can follow last the trend and
try to follow up to
to to fit it in, I think.
>> Exa- exactly.
>> Exactly. Yes, yes, exactly. Okay.
>> It works. Join your last the funding
round. Oh, I have no idea about
>> [laughter]
>> it. So, Nytra is now looking at Asia,
too. So, how do you see the health care
tech opportunities in Asia? Uh
including Taiwan, and what What is the
biggest difference compared to US
market?
>> mean I mean there's a there's huge
differences, right? And and um
>> Yeah.
>> I mean uh correct me if I'm wrong, by
the way, like I believe US is like
uh or Taiwan's probably I think the
number one, if not like definitely the
top three health care systems, right?
Whereas the US is probably like 40 or
50.
>> Yeah.
>> Right? So, it's really, really bad. Um I
would say the major difference is the
way that we do insurance, right?
Insurance is more
uh decentralized in US, whereas in
Taiwan it's very, very streamlined and
centralized.
>> Um so, a lot of problems there you guys
don't have. So, but that's actually
where majority of the problems are.
And there's like so many billion dollar
startups are just created just because
of this.
>> Yes.
>> Right? Um but there's still like issues
in general in in health care um
uh in general it's still on like the
spending side. Right? How do we do that
more efficiently?
Um how do we do that? Um
and measure that against like the demand
in in terms of patients and and the
drugs that are coming in. I still think
that I still think that translates over
to most of um just
the markets all across the world
anyways.
Um we still have to explore. I mean
we, you know, we do have a lot of
investors in in Taiwan. We have some
investors in Korea,
as well. And we do have like the doors
open to us to start talking to folks in
the healthcare space.
But, um, and we are going to talk with
them probably next year.
>> Mhm.
>> And
and start exploring where we can bring
our AI technology um, to see, you know,
how we can um
I guess make things a little bit better
and more efficient. But, right now it's
still early and I I don't have an exact
like product roadmap at this moment.
>> Okay.
>> You and team one has been friends since
elementary school, according to our
information. And you've been work
together through high school and
starting companies and for almost like
30 years.
And looking back, which is the secret to
keeping your partnership going for so
long?
>> Yeah, you know, that's a good question.
I I think
>> when you two don't agree, how do you
make the final call?
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah,
>> [laughter]
>> that is a great question that I think a
lot of people always wonder, right? Like
Uh, I mean, just for context, I we've
known each other since we're nine.
>> Wow, nine.
>> Uh, I'm 34 right now, so we've
>> [laughter]
>> So, 25 years, I think. It's 25 years.
So, you know, we've known each other for
25 years.
Um
and we were always good friends. Uh,
middle school, elementary school, middle
school, high school. Uh, he went to
Princeton. Um, I went to a local state
school in in in Maryland. Um, and
I guess like we synced up uh, our junior
year and we we started FiscalNote
together.
And I was the CTO, he was the CEO. Uh,
so technically, you know, he he was the
uh, um,
uh, the final decision maker and the
boss, right? So, I'll tell you when we
first started
>> Mhm.
>> we fought a lot. Like we like for 2
years we'd fight
just a lot, like
>> [laughter]
>> uh
cuz he wasn't uh so he did study
computer science, but he wasn't like
feeling the tech. So, he was dealing
with a lot of investors and dealing with
a lot of like
>> Yeah.
>> um customers. I was just purely focused
on the product
and engineering. Which in hindsight, I
was the wrong one, by the way. After
After uh yeah, no, like after being in
this role,
>> Yeah.
>> I realized I was definitely the wrong
one. [laughter]
No, but like uh cuz the difference
between like a CEO and CTO, people think
they're they're sort of like same cuz
like they're co-founders.
>> Mhm.
>> But there's a huge difference. Like CEO
is like way, way above. Um and the CTO
and like the CEO or like the everyone
else is like uh like below, like for
sure. And they have to worry about
significantly less.
>> Mhm.
>> The CEO has to
context switch every hour.
Every hour they're dealing with
customers, then they get pulled to
investors, then they get pulled to
engineering issues, then they get pulled
to, you know, product stuff. And it's
like significantly more difficult. Um
especially like mentally.
>> Yeah.
>> Whereas engineering, I just have to
focus on, oh, I guess the engineering
stuff. And there's no context switching
as much.
>> Mhm.
>> Um
so
in the beginning we fought a lot, but I
think
over time as cuz we dealt with so many
different issues,
I started to realize cuz I we were also
younger. So, we were like 21. So, very
immature. We never really worked
for like a major company, right? Um
but as you make million-dollar mistakes,
you know, you start to
think a lot more
about those mistakes.
And I think after the two or three year
It's probably two-year mark. Um
I started to realize, you know, and be
more mature about like, okay,
we have to have a hierarchy. We have to
have decision-making like um clarity,
right? Um and in order for this company
if it's starting to get to, you know,
many dozens to hundreds of people to
operate effectively, there needs to be a
chain of command and there needs to be,
um, disagree and commit. And because
like even if you're wrong, it doesn't
really matter. And we've been wrong
multiple times, right?
>> Right.
>> Um, what I realized over the years it
doesn't matter if you're wrong or right.
You have to make a decision, you go for
it, and then you fix the mistakes as
quickly as possible. So,
we started to do that and you know, I
already know like it just worked out so
much better.
>> Mhm.
>> So now like, I mean, so back then I was
like, all right. Like Tim and I would
talk about some issue, we'd disagree,
and then we'd talk about uh,
kind of like the the arguments both
sides and then Tim makes the final
decision and I'm like, okay, fine.
>> Mhm.
>> So now I just don't even like, I just be
like, hey, here's my concerns. I don't
think we should do this because of this.
And he'd be like, I understand, but
we're going to do this. And I'd be like,
okay, fine.
>> So so mature.
>> [laughter]
>> So it's yeah, so maturity came on later,
but it's after
making millions of dollars of mistakes.
Just letting you know.
Um,
so yeah, that's how we operate today, by
the way.
>> So uh, you have won awards like uh, 30
under 30 and DC 40 under 40.
For like a Asian American like you, uh,
what do you think these things that is
more easily misunderstood or
uh, what do they most
need to work hard to overcome in the
American tech world?
>> So the uh, um, I guess like what I've
noticed,
um,
I mean, there's there's definitely a lot
of challenges in
what's
uh, people don't really see or I guess
understand is like
it it is still even though like, you
know, I guess like people assume that
oh, if you're in America, you know,
there's a lot of opportunities and
stuff, right? Like
um, I guess that's that's true, but
I'll tell you, uh, Uh, in America like
if we're Asian-American, as an example,
um
we're not we don't belong to we we sort
of like are awkwardly in the middle,
like between Taiwan and and America.
Like, Americans don't see us as American
citizens. They actually don't, like the
white people, right? They just don't.
They see us as Asians. And then, when I
come back to Taiwan sometimes, you know,
obviously like, okay, maybe we look
Asian, but then they're like, oh,
they're Asian-American. So, we're not
we're sort of cut in this in between.
And then,
um so, if we we always feel like we
don't belong to both sides, but we
belong to both sides. So, it's this
weird this weird dynamic. And then, in
America,
because like, you know,
Americans or like
the sort of white Americans, they they
sort of treat us as, you know, like, oh,
these guys are smart anyways, they don't
need a lot of help.
Um and, you know, that's why all the
schools have all these like
discrimination, like the top schools,
right? You probably Everyone's probably
seen this, right? Like Harvard and like
Stanford and maybe not Stanford, but
like like the Ivies, they
they have like these
unspoken quotas of how many Asians are
allowed, right? Um and no matter how
much they deny it, it's 100% like true,
right? Um and it's been proven in in
court, too, right?
>> Yeah, yeah, yeah. I read the news. Yeah.
>> Yeah, right? So, it's it's So, like we
we have to literally work twice as hard
to get to the same place.
Um and a lot of Asian-Americans, they
come from immigrant families. So, a lot
of times when they their parents come
here, they come with nothing. So, they
have to not only work from no like
resources and no background, no
connections. They have to work twice as
hard just to even break into that type
of world, right? Well, the uh Americans,
like usually the white Americans who've
been there for generations, they already
have the connections, the foundation.
It's easier for them to get into like
the top schools and like the top
companies because like maybe their
uncle's already worked there, right?
It's like it the advantage is on that
side is just so much
uh well,
you know, I mean, it's not That's just
the way it is, right? Like, cuz they've
been in the country for a lot longer.
>> Yeah.
>> Right? So, they they just have more of a
head start. Whereas, us Asian Americans,
we it's getting better now because I
think we as a generation, the
millennials, and
like we worked extremely hard to
to kind of break into the society. So, I
think our children, the next generation,
will have it a lot better. Um,
but I think what people don't notice is
like, yes, I mean, you see all these
successful uh, potential, you know,
Asian founders and everything. But, it's
like, holy cow.
>> Yeah, Justin Wu. [laughter] I mean, but
it's like, holy cow, like the barriers
that were set for us in the and sort of
like the the unspoken racism that is
accepted in America because for some
reason it's okay to be racist towards
Asians, but it's not okay to be racist
towards like black people. Like, they
will not touch black people
um, in terms of anything racial. But,
then they'll make fun of Asians left and
right in media.
>> Mhm.
>> Right? So, that's sort of like the
unfortunate dynamic there.
>> Uh, so you will study and R&D department
in Taiwan. Speaking of Taiwan,
uh, what's your thought process? Why are
you opening an office here in Taiwan?
>> It it's a mix of of many different
reasons. Like,
um,
you know,
building a startup is definitely hard,
right? So, like, obviously, the obvious
reason that
uh, is it's definitely more
cost-effective. But, you can bring that
argument even further and say, "Well,
then why don't you put it like in
Vietnam or like go put your R&D team
like Indonesia or like the Philippines?"
And you know, then it goes to like
uh, more personal reasons. So, the
secondary reason is just like, well, I'm
Taiwanese American. My parents came from
Taiwan.
Um, I love Taiwan, too. I think it's
great talent. I also think it has
potential or it's starting to to become
sort of like the next like uh, big
startup uh,
kind of uh,
country like like Singapore. Singapore
right now is like they're pushing
startups. A lot of great startups are
coming out of there and the government's
pushing that. I think there's really
prime opportunity for Taiwan to showcase
our talent. I mean, we're like the best
in hardware right now
and that's not so far from software when
you really think about it.
And there's just a lot of great
opportunities
for Taiwan to really showcase the talent
but not a lot of companies are sort of
bringing their talent there in terms of
software and even internally the startup
kind of
I guess culture is still in its infancy.
And you have great folks like
you know,
the great tech leaders like Jensen or
like Jerry Yang and like Steve Chen.
They're trying to kind of
bring more of the the startup vibe right
in Taiwan and I sort of want to also
jump on that bandwagon. I want to come
and also push that. But those guys are
retired, right? So then
>> [laughter]
>> Right, so I'm the one who has to like,
"Okay, well, be a a a current example of
how I can bring a company here."
Um
uh try to hire as many great Taiwanese
talent and not just for Nitra but like
also showcase we do like we're trying to
make a lot of company culture videos to
show what's like to work at a startup
not just work at Nitra and encourage
sort of the next generation of folks to
one either join a startup
or try to start their own. Um and then
I'm just going to try to bring
as many like the American resources in
terms of experience but also in terms of
like maybe investors as well over to
Taiwan. So it's it's a also an innate
desire to push Taiwan upwards on the map
on a global scale. So multiple reasons.
>> Sounds great. You started in New York
not in Silicon Valley. So how did that
change things for fundraising, for
hiring, for industrial connections?
Looking back, you how do you feel about
that choice today?
>> Yeah.
Um
so I think uh
>> uh
I I don't know if this is true, but I
think I think this is true. I think the
perception like if you're in the New
York if you're in New York or in in SF
or the Bay Area, I think the the term
Silicon Valley startup is all the same.
Um because like
you know, a lot of if you're a top uh
Silicon Valley startup, you're probably
based in one of the two cuz all the
major startups are based in those two
cities at least in America, right?
>> Mhm.
>> I mean, you know, a good example would
probably be like Ramp. Ramp is based in
New York, but everyone views it as
Silicon Valley startup. Right?
>> But they are financial startup.
>> Yeah.
>> Okay.
>> Um and like for us like at Nitro, we are
financial startup, too. So, we're also
built in
New York City.
>> Yeah.
>> So, I mean, it makes a lot more sense to
us. I think if you're like a true AI
company, you're probably based in
the Valley, but it's okay to be based in
New York cuz I'll tell you like
New York City is like if you're in any
industry, New York is really good.
Um because if you're anybody who's
important or like investor or like a
major customer, you're going to you're
you're flying through New York City at
least once a year. So, you can expect
certain people like that you probably
need to talk to, they're always going to
come through uh
um New York City every single year. But
actually, that's not I don't think
that's true for Silicon Valley. I think
that's true for investors, they always
pass through SF. But if you're talking
about customers or like suppliers or all
these folks,
um different type of stakeholders, they
won't be passing through Silicon Valley.
I personally think New York is a
you know,
great place to build a startup. But of
course, like the perception is AI
startup should probably be in Silicon
Valley, right?
>> Yeah. Okay.
So, uh looking
three
to five years ahead, uh how far do you
think AI will go inside
Click?
Which jobs will be fully automate? And
uh which jobs will actually come back to
humans?
>> That is a really good question.
>> [sighs]
>> A big question.
>> That is a big question.
>> Yeah.
>> Um
Man, I've been I've been I've been just
giving you guys an idea of what I've
been doing. Uh I've been playing around
with a lot of like the coding tools,
right?
>> Yeah.
>> And yeah, I mean it it's it's pretty
it's really really good and it's
changing really fast. Like, I feel like
the whole design industry is like really
screwed. Um
>> Oh.
>> Because of crowd design.
>> [laughter]
>> Well, it's just like just everything in
that direction. Coding is
to me, the shift in coding is like
similar to when like probably C was
invented. I don't know if you know like
before
programming languages were the way that
they were, where you type more English
words.
>> Yeah.
>> Before that, I think it was like 1970,
before 1970, it was like machine
language and like something called
assembly, where it's really really hard
to understand. And then they invented C.
>> Mhm.
>> And then then it's like a whole shift.
>> Yeah.
>> So now you even you change how to
program. So I think we're
we're seeing that shift again. It's just
now it's just pure English.
>> Yeah.
>> Or pure like, you know, language.
>> Natural language.
>> Exactly.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> Um I still think programming's going to
be there. You have to understand sort of
it's more of like constructing an essay.
>> Mhm.
>> Right? Like writing now. Um
it will still be a job, probably a lot
less people.
>> Mhm.
>> I do think the same thing with um
design. It's just
everything's just a lot less people,
right? Um product managers probably have
a lot more power now. They don't need as
many engineers
anymore.
Um you still need people to do critical
thinking, um management, um but I do
think
>> Communicate.
>> Communication is still
>> Communication is yeah.
>> still a huge thing. Management is
probably going to start
kind of fading away cuz you're probably
cuz you have less people in the company
now, right? Probably. Um usually when
you hit like eight people on a team then
you need a manager, right? Eight to 10
people. But if your team is only eight
people in general, then why do you need
a manager? So right? So like that
position is probably going to start um
fading away.
Um
yeah, I mean
definitely like what Open AI what what
Sam said, right? Like you're going to
start seeing just a lot of like small
companies operating with small teams,
but then they have tremendous amount of
revenue.
>> Yeah.
>> So that's probably what's going to
happen.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. But but I mean what do
we have inside the clinics?
>> Oh, the clinics?
>> Yeah, your clinics.
Uh
I think the new uh working flow will
>> Yeah.
>> enhance uh what they are doing. But the
it's still hard to image what will
change in next maybe
5 years, I think.
>> Yeah.
Honestly,
so you use
>> [laughter]
>> It's probably like I I think
I think
we just don't need like the traditional
doctors anymore.
>> Oh.
>> Right?
>> Yeah.
>> Cuz like most people even right now you
just you just ask ChatGPT or Claude like
about your illness. And I feel like I
mean to be honest, um not to
um say anything bad about like doctors,
but I feel like half of them are kind of
just like
you know, they're probably Googling
stuff in the background anyways.
And
I think you definitely need surgeons,
right? But then that may be replaced by
machines eventually, but maybe that'll
take a little bit longer.
>> Yeah. Robotic arms or something.
>> Yeah, but like
I mean medicine's just going to be
accelerated significantly. Um I mean
definitely the office manager jobs are
going to going to go, right? Cuz it's
going to be easier to manage that. The
only reason why those would stay is
because of regulations. Um outside of
that, people are probably going to start
consulting AI more.
You know, on just like basic health
issues and like sick illnesses.
Uh and then
probably the major like surgical or like
procedural
um items will be left to the those type
of doctors, you know, the the major like
um high-profile doctors. That's that's
what I think.
>> So,
I it's supposed uh night hour will
um deals the most of process of the the
job, I think, I guess.
>> Yeah, I think for this So,
you know, one time I was asked like,
"Oh, what is the 20-year horizon?" Yeah,
yeah. Like like
>> [laughter]
>> So, I think if you're as a company, you
know, you do have to think like very
strategically. You can't um you have to
think very far in the future. So, the
first step is like we automate the
entire back office. Um
try to reduce the amount of like uh
processes there, right? From from the
the patient scheduling all the way to
the the ordering everything. So, like
we're basically replacing the eventually
5 years from now, right? We basically
replace like the office managers.
Um
then I think I mean the doctors itself
will probably be slowly be replaced by
just AI in general cuz then people would
start stop seeing doctors. They would
just like for for example, like my derma
like my skin,
I'll probably just be able to like take
a picture of it and then get what's
wrong, right? From just sending it to
the AI. So, why do I need to go to see a
dermatologist anymore? And then ask like
what medicine do I need. And then maybe
I need they they say you need this
medicine.
Um
so, that but you have to be prescribed,
which is why I said regulations is still
a big thing. So, then I have to go to a
doctor to actually get the prescription.
Um so, that's probably still a huge
barrier in itself.
>> It sounds so sci-fi.
>> [laughter]
>> Okay. Um
I think it's uh
this is the this is the last part is all
casual talk. So can you
you have
taken a company from zero to IPO and now
raised
over
100 million again. Can you share your
personal some financial
philosophy?
How do you
spread your money between cash, stock or
stock
in stock investing?
>> investment
>> Oh, you mean your personal philosophy?
>> yeah, your personal
opinion, your your not advice, just
share the philosophy.
>> experience.
>> Yeah.
Uh, you know,
I think there was a period of time where
I did do day trading.
>> [laughter]
>> Sorry for a year during COVID and then
made a lot of money and then I lost a
decent amount of money, too.
>> [laughter]
>> Uh, but I I like it
Now like my personal philosophy nowadays
is like
um
Remember, I I'm I'm not like a heavy
like crazy trader or anything. But I did
dive into that for a period of time.
Um
I think just for me it's like I do
investing just like
like what do you call it like the the
sort of like um there's a term for it.
Uh
like the the dollar cost averaging type
of investing. So as in like I don't
spend time looking at anything more. I
just kind of just invest every like
automated in certain stocks that I like
every like week or two weeks.
And then just let it go. Because like
I've always realized even just 10 years
ago if I if I just did this, I would
have made more money
>> Yeah.
>> instead of just trying to day trade and
make it crap ton money faster.
>> Yeah, so
just keep it investing. How do you up
living?
>> Yeah.
>> Because in 10 years it's probably going
to significantly jump.
>> Yes.
>> have to be patient.
>> And I regret now because I'm if I had
just done that for 10 years, like
freaking Amazon, Facebook, they all
jumped 10x. It's like
>> This is my This is my experience too
because
when I build my first company maybe 15
years ago and then
we believe in Google, believe in Apple,
believe in Amazon. So, we should just
invest them and they are all 10x right
now.
>> [laughter]
>> And Nvidia too, right?
Like
>> It's not obvious. What do you do that
again right now?
>> Because everyone's trying to make They
see other people make a lot of money and
they all try to want to make quick
money.
>> Yeah.
>> So, then they try to do this day trade
like oh, what what can we do with like,
you know, option trading and like,
>> crypto things
>> crypto stuff. Everyone's trying to make
money quickly. So, therefore they don't
and they miss out on the truly stable
way to make money.
>> And what do we truly believe in?
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah, yeah.
>> You just have to be more patient. 5-10
year horizon.
>> Yeah.
>> Okay.
>> Um with such a busy work life, how do
you relax? Is there any hobby or sport
that you always make time for?
>> Yeah.
Sports, I don't have time for sports.
>> Really? Oh.
>> Uh but I mean I like like martial arts.
I used to do martial arts when I was a
kid.
>> Okay.
>> Uh
Like if if someone like if if a friend
challenge me challenges me to a fight,
I'll I'll I'll fight them for fun.
>> Yeah, okay.
>> Um but but what I truly do is I watch
anime.
I watch a lot of anime.
>> What Do you have any recommendations?
>> Oh man, I mean
>> [laughter]
>> Well, I mean for the anime lovers, I
think My HERO ACADEMIA.
I DON'T know what the Chinese
Oh, yeah, yeah, that's right. Uh
obviously like the major ones like
Attack on Titan of course really good.
Death Note, one of the earlier ones.
Um
more like
I guess obscure ones like I like Kaiju
number eight.
That one's really good.
Yeah.
>> [laughter]
>> Uh I like solo leveling is good.
I know that one's really popular.
I mean I literally have a list.
>> [laughter]
>> And I like work and play them in the
background sometimes. Okay.
>> Um lately is there a book, a podcast, or
any interview you will recommend to our
listeners?
>> Yeah.
So my style is very different like I
don't have the patience to read books.
Uh but I do read a lot. Like I read
short like articles and things I
research.
Um
whenever there's a topic that I need to
dive into and
whether it's like marketing or sales, my
philosophy is like follow all the the
best like YouTubers, Instagrammers who
are talking about this and fill your
feed with that type of content.
Like right now like I'm studying a lot
of um
like marketing. Um and I did this with
sales, too. Like my entire feed right
now is just like all marketing tactics,
all social media tactics, all like you
know, uh you know, how to craft like
great hooks and like how to get people's
attention and keep people's attention.
Literally so when I'm scrolling I'm not
scrolling through like random content.
It's like when I'm you know, taking a
break looking at social media I'm like
learning always.
You know, that's like my philosophy and
then I think for people who don't like
to read books and sit down read books um
like how can you still keep learning?
Like that's my style. Like free time
everything I'm literally just learning.
I'm like I'm watching these videos like
oh, this is like the best way to do
this. Oh, this is the best way to do
this. So that that's that's how I do
things.
>> Okay. Uh Johnson, thank you so much for
joining us today.
Um if you want uh you
if you want to learn more about Night
Job and we will we will put the link in
the podcast
uh show note in the link. Johnson, thank
you again and hopefully you see you in
Taipei soon.
>> Yeah, I love Taiwan.
>> [laughter]
>> Thank you guys.
>> Thank you guys. Bye.
>> [music]
>> Bye-bye.